Hello Hello friends I am Ward's Design
Expert Welcome to Bagal Friends
today we will talk about if a person makes
a joint from his pocket and leaves his job
and after some time he feels that he has to join again then can
that person join that job
or not this was presented before the Delhi High Court
today we will talk about something do
watch it by video call so that you can get complete information
and if you have not subscribed to our channel yet then
subscribe now
and also press the bell icon and give
me a try
so friends this is the case of Moharram Ali
Khan vs Jamia Millia Islamia
University Entrance Test Case Maths in which the
petitioner said that he had gone to Saudi Arabia for
a project where he was
given the job of a professor and after 1 year when that
professor's work was over
he came to India after coming to India after coming to India
he applied for the result in the university where he had resigned but the
officials there rejected his application
He
filed a petition in the Delhi High Court stating that he had
gone to the university on February 17, 2010, for a project where he had been offered a
professorship. After completing his work,
he returned to India on August 25, 2011,
and wanted to be reinstated
in his full-time job and to replace Rizwan.
If this was not done, the
fundamental rights under
Article 9 of the Constitution (
Class 1) would be violated.
In response, the Jamia Millia Islamia University stated
that he had
resigned after careful consideration. His
resignation had been accepted, so
he could
no longer challenge Rizwan's resignation. The
court, taking both sides into
consideration, held that the petitioner did
not need to resign from the university for the Saudi Arabia project. The
petitioner should have
investigated the matter before resigning.  It should have been
taken
if a person gives this once
and it is also accepted
that Kapil cannot take it back, that is, it was a
huge victory for the petitioner,
along with the family of the petitioner, the court
rejected it, that is, if a person
resigns from his job, even if the resignation is
accepted, then it will
not be taken back, so this information
that if a person gives his resignation
and then later and he feels
that he wants to remit, then should
he do it or not, the
answer to this was that he may
not even get a chance to zoom, so friends,
do tell us how you liked the information, friends, if you liked
this video, then like it,
share it, if you have any question, you
can comment, friends, if you have
not yet subscribed to our channel, then
subscribe now and
also press the bell icon so that you can get instant notifications of news like Hai to Lal Mirch
aur Nickel videos,
along with this you can follow our social
media platforms Facebook, Twitter,
Instagram and Lingerie,
thank you for watching the full Karishma video,
A
Jhala  Jhal Jhal